# **MAAZ HUSSAIN**

# Mobile App Developer

On the way to pursue my goal to become a MERN stack developer. A motivated, determined and Highly skilled React Native developer with 1 year of experience in building and maintaining cross-platform mobile applications. Proficient in JavaScript, React, and experienced in integrating with APIs and third-party libraries. Strong problem-solving skills and attention to detail.



# **Work Experience**

COMPANY as ,Intern

DepChip, Karachi June 2021- Sep 2021

TechnikOrb, Karachi

March 2022- July 2022

**Jr.React Native Developer** 

(July 2022-Present)

At 82 Solutions, Karachi

"Developed and maintained crossplatform mobile applications using React Native , Worked with APIs and integrated third-party libraries."

Karachi, Pakistan

O332-2438836

hussainmaaz51@gmail.com

inkdin.com/Maazhussain

github.com/maazhussain8836





### Education

**BCS** 

2019-2023

**INTERMEDIATE** 

2017-2019

Sir Syed University, Karachi

Subject that I have studied in BCS are Database, Networking, OOP, Artificial Intelligence, and Computer Ethics.

Govt .Degree College Gulshan-e-Iqbal, Karachi (Pre -Engeneering)

**HTML** 

**Javascript** 

React Native

**CSS** 

Bootstrap

React

**Interest** 

Coding

Teaching

History

Badminton

Learning



### **Courses & Certifications**

**CLP** (2017)

Web-Developer **Bootcamp** 

(Present)

React JS (Present) MS-Office from (ITEC)

MERN stack learning course From (UDEMY).

Responsive layouts & React JS Full course from (Scrimba)

Languages

**English** 



Urdu

